meteoearth.com 2012-10-16

# MeteoEarth - powered by MeteoGroup

Your privacy is important to us. Any personal information you provide to us will be dealt with in accordance with this privacy policy. 

All of the MeteoGroup of companies* is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy explains our data processing practices and your options regarding the ways in which your personal data is used. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to our processing please contact us by sending an e-mail or write to us at: The Data Protection Officer, Legal Department, PA Group, 292 Vauxhall Bridge Road, London SW1V 1AE. 

Whenever you supply personal information to any MeteoGroup company we are obliged to deal with that information in a lawful way in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. 

We may request information from you in order to process your transaction, fulfil your order or provide you with the services and products you expect. This information may include, but is not limited to, details such as your name, your address, your e-mail address, telephone number and bank account details. If you subscribe to any MeteoGroup service or product we will use your personal information to provide you with the service or product you select (e.g. sending you password reminders or notices about the relevant service or product being suspended for emergency or routine maintenance). In addition, we may collect information from you, for example, in order to reply to any enquiry you make of any MeteoGroup company. We may use the information you provide for our own internal statistical purposes. 

We will not disclose any personal information you provide to us to any third party organisation outside the MeteoGroup of companies, unless we need to do so to provide you with the products or services you select or we are obliged or permitted by law to disclose it. 

Whenever you submit personal information to any MeteoGroup company you may opt out of receiving any further promotional material from the MeteoGroup of companies. If you wish to opt out of receiving any promotional material from any MeteoGroup company please contact the MeteoGroup personnel to whom you submitted your personal information or you may send an e-mail. However, if you do choose to have promotional material sent to you, you will be given the option to "unsubscribe" from receiving any further information about that product or service from us. 

If you wish to correct or update any of the personal details we hold about you, please contact your usual MeteoGroup contact as soon as possible or write to us at: The Data Protection Officer, Legal Department, PA Group, 292 Vauxhall Bridge Road, London SW1V 1AE. 

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information that we hold about you and have any inaccuracies corrected. Please address requests to: The Data Protection Officer, Legal Department, PA Group, 292 Vauxhall Bridge Road, London SW1V 1AE. 

When you visit any MeteoGroup company web site we may use "cookies". Cookies are text files that identify your computer to our server. Our web sites only use cookies to support and improve your experience of our websites. 

MeteoGroup web sites may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please note that, if you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours. 

"MeteoGroup" means MeteoGroup Limited (or any holding company of it) and each subsidiary from time to time of MeteoGroup Limited (or any holding company of it). 

_MeteoGroup is in the process of updating its Privacy Policy to provide you with easier information about the cookies on its websites. In the meantime, we would like to inform you that we make use of cookies. These are small files that are placed on your computer's hard disc to remember certain things about your use of our sites, for example remembering your stored preferences for our services or your login details. This is so you do not have to re-enter these details each time you use our service. We also make use of third party cookies such as but not limited to, Google Analytics. The cookies are anonymous and will not register any personal data such as your IP-address. You can decide to modify your browser settings so that cookies are not accepted. Further information can be found at www.aboutcookies.org._

**Meteo** Earth is a product of **Meteo** Graphics, the broadcast brand of **MeteoGroup**
